Chapter 2: The First Night

Several minutes later, Aishia accompanied Celia into the changing room beside the stone bathroom. In contrast to Celia, who removed her one piece dress in a hesitant manner, Aishia instantly released the material form of her clothes and stood in only her underwear.

“...Ah, that underwear’s made by the Ricca Guild, isn’t it?” Celia asked in a bright voice. She had gazed in amazement at how Aishia stripped in the blink of an eye before she realized the design of Aishia’s underwear seemed familiar.

“Yup, that’s right. Miharu chose it for me.” Aishia nodded. She was wearing a pale pink bra and boy shorts with small but cute and elegant ribbons on it.

“Miharu... that’s one of the girls Rio took in, right? It really is an adorable design. Can I feel what the fabric is like?” Celia asked with great interest.

“Sure,” Aishia agreed readily.

“Then if you don’t mind... Oh, and you have a really gorgeous figure, you know? Your skin is youthful and beautiful, too, just like a baby’s... Wait, we were talking about the underwear right now. Underwear...” Celia’s eyes were captivated by Aishia’s good proportions before she shook her head and reached for the underwear.

“Yup yup, this really is good quality fabric. Not only is it comfortable to wear, its design is well thought out. I also have several of these, but the Ricca Guild’s products are popular, so they always sell out of their low stock in the Beltrum Kingdom. It’s pretty hard to get your hands on them,” Celia said.

“They sell lots in Amande. You should just get Haruto to buy you some, too, since we’ll be going shopping in Amande tomorrow.”

“It’s the headquarters of the Ricca Guild, so I’m sure there’ll be lots in stock, but is it really okay? The underwear in the Ricca Guild is fairly expensive.”

“It’s fine. Haruto is rich,” Aishia said, giving her approval of Rio’s financial status.

“S-Still, it makes me feel bad having him buy expensive things for me... There are lots of other things I need to buy, too.” Celia frowned, feeling bad for causing trouble.

“Underwear is a necessity, so it wouldn’t be a wasteful purchase. And Haruto would want Celia to wear good quality underwear,” Aishia said on Rio’s behalf. There was no knowing what kind of expression Rio would have made if he was present, but he probably would have said something similar if he was pressed on the subject.

“A-Ahaha... W-Well, I can’t show Rio my underwear, b-but I’ll make sure to talk to him about it.” Celia must have pictured something in her mind, as her voice squeaked with embarrassment.

“Yup.” Aishia nodded, moving her hands to her bra to take it off.

“...Huh? Come to think of it, how come you have real underwear when your other clothes are all materialized...?” Celia suddenly noticed.

“Yeah. Underwear is complicated to make.”

“Oh, I see... So you can’t make anything complicated.”

“Actually, it’s more like the clothes I usually wear are a part of myself. I can change the color and design a little, but I generally can’t create anything else,” Aishia said, giving a concise explanation of her materialized clothes.

“Huh...” Celia hummed with deep curiosity.

“Let’s get in already,” Aishia said, sliding off her boy shorts in one go before heading toward the bathroom.

...S-She’s a rather bold girl, isn’t she? She doesn’t seem to care about what others think at all. Celia couldn’t help but blush at the sight of the beautiful body that entered her line of vision. However, she had no reason to remain in the changing room by herself, so she took off her cute minisole that she’d been wearing as underwear and headed toward the bathroom, too.

◇　◇　◇

When Celia opened the door that led from the changing room to the bathroom, she looked around the room and froze.

“What... is this place...?”

The sight of the bathroom interior far surpassed anything she had pictured in her mind. It was a wide, spacious room; the walls were bare stone, long in depth and with a high ceiling. Beyond the spacious washing area that was tiled with stone was a wide bathtub, also made of stone. The water spouting artifacts lined along the stone wall continuously supplied hot water, making a white steam rise off the surface of the bathwater. Celia stood in dumbfounded amazement for a while.

“It’s a bath...?” Aishia answered Celia’s question, tilting her head to the side.

“...A-Ah, no, I can see that, but... What?!” Celia objected in a fluster. It was clearly different to a traditional bathroom in the Strahl region.

At the very least, it wasn’t the standard for bathtubs to be deep enough to immerse oneself. Not even the royalty and nobility had bathing facilities this fancy, and it wasn’t possible for them to make hot water come pouring out endlessly as it did here. The climate of the region was rather dry, so they couldn’t secure a water source that could be used so wastefully. It’d be a different matter in a land with hot springs, but nothing like that existed in Beltrum or Beltrant.

“What’s wrong?” Aishia asked Celia curiously.

“W-What do you mean ‘what’? What’s going on with this bath...? What is this — why is the hot water flowing endlessly?” Celia asked, pointing at the stone wall where the water was refilling the bathtub.

“That’s a magic artifact that makes hot water,” Aishia replied.

“A m-magic artifact... No, but... How is the essence supplied to it?! If the hot water is continuously being created, wouldn’t the essence consumption be ridiculously high?”

Celia’s question was reasonable; water sorcery already used a higher amount of magic essence than the other elemental sorceries, but to have a spell formula that created water and heated it up at the same time would use even more essence than that. If it was left running around the clock, it would continue using up essence much like a snowball effect.

“A high quality spirit stone is being used as the core of all the magic artifacts in the house, so as long as that one is replenished with essence regularly, it’s fine,” Aishia answered easily.

“Spirit stone... That’s another term I haven’t heard of before.”

Celia sighed tiredly. Even though she had come to the bathroom to wash away her tiredness, it seemed to have the reverse effect on her.

“Come. I’ll teach you how to use the artifact,” Aishia beckoned in a calm voice.

“...Okay.” Celia put on a smile of resignation and followed Aishia, deciding to put herself at ease for now. Aishia then explained how to use the hot water artifacts placed along the bathtub. “Before you submerge yourself in the water, you first wash your body and hair. This is the soap.”

At Aishia’s suggestion, they started to wash their bodies first. She handed Celia a bottle with body wash inside.

Celia removed the lid from the bottle she received and checked the inside, her eyes widening quite a bit. “Huh? This is soap...? Wait, isn’t this a liquid?! And it smells really nice too!” She was even more stunned after sniffing the scent of the soap.

In the Strahl region, solid soap was the standard. On top of that, it was already considered a high class item — despite the quality itself being only so-so. It often smelled rather bad, too.

“I heard that the Ricca Guild was extending their hand toward the development of soap, but...” Perhaps it was because there had been issues in the development process, or the stock had simply been too low, Celia thought.

“This soap was made by Haruto.”

Celia’s eyes widen in shock. “Huh, really?!”

“Yeah. He made all kinds of soap while Miharu and the others were here. Miharu has approved of the quality of each one.” Shampoo, conditioner, body wash, and maybe a face wash was enough if it were just a man living alone, but with Miharu and Aki around, Rio tried to make all the varieties of soap he learned to create in the village.

“Huh... T-Then, can I use it right away?” Celia asked with great interest. She was also interested in this Miharu girl whose name kept on coming up, but right now, her curiosity was piqued toward the unknown but nice-smelling soap.

“Of course. What do you usually wash first? Your hair, body, or face?”

“Huh? Umm, maybe face? I have some light makeup on from the ceremony still.”

“Then use this one.” Aishia handed Celia the bottle with cleanser in it.

She first started with cleansing her face; after slowly and carefully washing off her makeup, she next washed her hair and body.

“Wow! My hair and skin feel completely different! It’s so much better than normal!” Celia said with a fully satisfied expression after everything had been washed.

“Let’s get into the bath, then,” Aishia suggested.

“Okay!” Celia replied cheerfully. Wrapping her hair up in a steamed towel, she carried her feet over to the bathtub and got inside it with Aishia.

“Wah, hah...” At the sensation of the hot water wrapping around her body, Celia unthinkingly let out a coquettish sound.

“So warm.” Aishia also smiled happily beside her.

“...I could get used to this.” Celia sank into the bath water and completely relaxed her entire body, letting the stress drain out. It was her first time sitting in a bath this large and deep.

“You can come here every day from here on out, you know,” Aishia said.

“I see... I look forward to it,” Celia giggled with a smile.

...It still doesn’t feel real, she thought sentimentally. Was it really okay for her to be this happy? When she thought about the family she left behind in the kingdom, guilt rose up within her and made her frown.

“From now on, you can think about the future with Haruto.” Aishia must have noticed the slight change in Celia’s expression, prompting her to speak. Celia widened her eyes.

“...Yeah, thank you. You always seem to be aloof, but you’re actually rather sharp, aren’t you?”

“That’s not true.” Aishia shook her head slowly. Suddenly, Celia grinned widely. “Hey, Aishia. I know you only woke up recently, but do you know anything about the past Rio?” she asked.

“I know everything there is to know about Haruto.”

“Umm, does that mean you have memories from when you were asleep, too?”

“No. It’s just that the things Haruto saw and heard flowed into me through our contract’s connection.”

Celia’s eyes widened in surprise. “...That’s amazing. I don’t know about ancient sorcery, but that’s an art that cannot be done in modern day sorcery, for sure.”

“It’s hard even with spirit arts. Telepathy is one thing, but sharing memories between each other requires quite a high level of mind synchronization.”

“I see. ...Hm? But isn’t that... It sounds like you’re saying that your consciousness and Rio’s consciousness are strongly tied together, almost...?” It was something Celia couldn’t overlook.

“That’s what a spirit contract is. We’re spiritually bound together on a soul level,” Aishia agreed bluntly.

“Wha...” Celia was at a loss for words. T-That’s not fair! she thought in her mind. Aishia tilted her head curiously.

Celia met Aishia’s eyes; fearing she had been seen through, she flinched, before purposefully changing the subject. “T-That aside, Rio’s been able to use spirit arts since his days in the academy, right?”

“Yup. He was self-taught, so his technical skills were a little clumsy, but he worked hard at it by himself,” Aishia agreed with a nod.

“I-I see. He never showed any sign of that, so I never noticed, but he really worked hard...” Celia smiled somewhat wistfully. Considering how out of the ordinary spirit arts was, her judgment made sense... though she was a little sad that he hid it from her at the time.

“The reason why Haruto didn’t tell you wasn’t because he didn’t trust you,” Aishia uttered simply. She’d hit the nail on the head.

“I-I know that. It isn’t something to tell someone for no reason, and even telling someone trustworthy can be risky. Rio isn’t that kind of person. That is, how should I put it...”

“Even when he’s in trouble, he doesn’t really rely on others. He tries to solve it himself,” Aishia pointed out, making Celia nod along furiously.

“Yes, like that!”

“But, he’s a little different from before. He’s still a little shy about it, but he’s starting to rely on others more,” Aishia said regarding Rio’s growth, which was something that Celia was unaware of.

“Huh, is that so... So he’s grown up that much in the time we were apart...” Celia’s eyes widened in interest as she watched Aishia with envy in her eyes.

“It’s thanks to Celia,” Aishia said.

“R-Really?” Celia blinked, looking shocked.

“Yup. Of course, part of it was also because he met lots of warm people on his journey and grew close to them, but the first person to show Haruto kindness was Celia. Celia stayed beside Haruto throughout his whole academy life,” Aishia said, showing a rare smile.

“...” Celia found herself captivated by Aishia’s soft, warm smile without realizing it.

“Please be kind to Haruto, as you always have,” Aishia said in conclusion.

“...Fufu, of course I will.” Celia smiled gently, nodding happily.

Chapter 4: Infiltrating the Claire Estate

That same day, after returning to the stone house, Celia shut herself in her allocated room and began to write a letter. The addressee was, of course, her family.

As she painfully pondered over how much she should say and what to write other than informing them of her safety, the contents of the letter gradually progressed. Several hours after she began writing, a letter with an acceptable amount of content recorded in it was completed.

She wanted to sleep over it for a night before proofreading, but for now, she read over it again to make sure there weren’t any glaring problems.

“...It’s done.”

Celia breathed deeply and put her quill down on the desk. She stretched her arms and stood up from the chair, heading for the door. When she opened the door and moved to the living room, Rio and Aishia were sitting on the sofa, chatting. The two of them immediately noticed Celia’s presence.

“Did you finish writing your letter, Professor?” Rio asked Celia. She nodded.

“Yup, for now. I’d like you to read it to make sure there’s no issues with the contents...” she said timidly.

“Sure, I don’t mind doing that.”

“Thanks. Here you go.”

Rio accepted the letter from Celia and ran his eyes over the text. “Your writing is as neat as expected, Professor,” he said, breaking into a smile.

“G-Geez. Don’t look at that... Are there any problems with the contents?” Celia asked with red cheeks.

“...No, nothing I’m seeing. It’s a very warm letter.”

“I-I see. Thank you.” Celia accepted the letter with embarrassment.

“We were actually just discussing the journey to Count Claire’s territory. I was thinking of setting up base in the outskirts of Amande for a while and departing the day after tomorrow, but there’s somewhere I’d like to stop by on our way back,” Rio said.

“I don’t mind. Where do you want to go?” Celia asked.

“Marquess Rodan’s territory — the capital of Rodania.”

“The headquarters of the Duke Huguenot faction, which has Princess Flora right now... You’re going to check on the background of the hero that was summoned, aren’t you?” Celia asked, immediately making a guess as to why Rio was heading for Rodania.

“I’m glad you’re quick on the uptake.” Rio grinned widely and nodded.

Yesterday, he had heard from Celia that there were four kingdoms that had sacred stones which summoned heroes: One in the Kingdom of Beltrum, one with the Huguenot faction that had been exiled from Beltrum, one in the Kingdom of Galarc, and one in the kingdom of Centostella. Out of these four, the only one whose name had been identified was the hero of the Beltrum Kingdom, Rui Shigekura. Thus, Rio was considering confirming the name of the hero from the Huguenot faction on their way to Count Claire’s territory.

“I’m sure there’s no need for me to say anything to the two of you, but be careful, okay?” Celia said, timidly peering at Rio and Aishia’s faces.

“We will. For now, our goal is to simply confirm the hero’s name, so we won’t do anything too dangerous,” Rio agreed readily, trying not to worry Celia.

“...In other words, you won’t approach the Rodania hero even if they turn out to be the hero you’re looking for?”

“If that turns out to be the case, I’ll make a careful decision based on the situation of their security. I don’t know if they’ll be willing to listen to the words of an intruder appearing out of nowhere, and if the worst happens and a battle occurs, I don’t know what kind of abilities the hero might be hiding. They’re a complete unknown.” It wasn’t as though he was visiting an acquaintance, so he wasn’t about to go looking for trouble.

“The hero’s abilities, huh? You might know this already, but there’s a legend... That they had Divine Arms of the gods and could defeat a demon army of several thousand in a single blow. Or so it’s said,” Celia said.

“...Did the hero summoned in Beltrum’s castle, Rui Shigekura, have a power like the legends?” Rio asked curiously. A legend was just a legend — there was no guarantee it was true. However, heroes of legend were actually appearing in the present, so it wasn’t impossible to find out.

“I don’t know the details, but he did have a Divine Arms. In Rui Shigekura’s case, his took the shape of a weapon — a bow. One that can control lightning, or something.”

“Divine Arms in the form of a lightning bow...” Rio muttered quietly.

Don’t tell me the attack he launched that time was...

Something familiar came to Rio’s mind. When he was acting as a diversion for Celia to safely escape the capital, the boy had fired a shot at him from the top of a steeple.

“Is something the matter?” Celia looked at Rio’s face curiously.

Rio shook his head. “No. Did that Divine Arms really have the power to defeat a huge demon army, like you said?” he asked. He didn’t want to say that he had possibly crossed swords with the hero, since Celia would just worry.

“I don’t know. Even if he could release a shot with that much power, it isn’t something you can use just anywhere...”

“Well, that’s true,” Rio accepted with a wry smile. At worst, the landscape could change.

“Yeah, but...” Celia paused with a frown, causing Rio to urge her to continue.

“But?”

“Do you remember how I was developing an artifact that could measure the essence stored inside a person?” Celia suddenly changed the topic with a question for Rio.

“Of course.”

“I actually succeeded not too long ago.”

Rio’s eyes widened. “...Congratulations. That’s amazing... quite a historic achievement.”

The development of a magic artifact that could measure the amount of essence within a person was a challenge that had yet to be accomplished, until now.

Celia shyly burst into a wide smile before immediately looking troubled and continuing her story. “Thank you. Because of that, I actually used that artifact to measure the magic essence of the hero and his friends that were summoned along with him...”

“How was the result?” Rio asked with a serious expression, matching the mood of her story with his own enthusiasm.

“...They all had so much essence, it was immeasurable. The artifact broke. Even though I made it capable of measuring up to ten times the amount of essence required to use wide-scale annihilation magic of the highest grade...” Celia said with a conflicted look.

The type of magic she had brought up referred to the super-powerful grand magic that was mainly developed with war in mind. If used in a crowded area, it had enough power to take the lives of several hundred people. However, on top of the compatibility rate of the spell formula contract being low, it also exhausted a ridiculous amount of magic essence, requiring more essence than the average sorcerer could use.

“I see. Not only the hero, but his friends were also unable to be measured in essence...” In that case, Miharu and the others might have quite the amount of essence too, Rio thought.

“I’ve never seen wide-scale annihilation magic used before. Is it as much as your essence, Professor?” Rio asked about Celia’s essence amount to gain an idea of how much a genius sorcerer would have.

“Without any essence recovery potions, I can cast it twice, at most. Just so you know, I’m the sorcerer with the most magic essence in the Beltrum Kingdom, okay?” Celia sighed, answering with a bitter smile.

“So even for you, the limit is two...” Rio tapped his hand against his mouth in contemplation.

“Haruto’s essence is limitless,” Aishia murmured quietly.

“...Really?” Celia’s eyes widened as she looked at Rio’s face inquisitively.

“No... I wonder? I’ve been told I have a lot, but I’ve never measured it properly.” Rio scratched his head, troubled.

“It’s an endless supply, so it’s limitless. If Celia’s essence was a single bucket of water, then Haruto’s essence is like an endlessly large lake that can never dry up. Miharu, Aki, and Masato have lots, too, but not as much as Haruto,” Aishia said, using a metaphor to explain the scale of Rio’s magic essence.

“A-Ahaha... That’s incredible.” Celia’s smile twitched in spite of herself.

If that was the truth, then it was absurd for her to compare herself with him. The statement was slightly hard to believe, but despite their short time together, she knew Aishia wasn’t the type to lie without a reason to do so.

“...Huh? Wait a minute. Why do you know how much essence Rio has?” Celia suddenly questioned out loud, looking at Aishia.

“Spirits can tell how much magic essence a person has by diving into them. Haruto and I are connected by a spirit path, so I can read his essence amount more accurately than I can with others. Even so, I can’t see his limit.”

“...You mean even you can’t measure his essence amount accurately?” Celia confirmed timidly. Aishia gave a short nod.

“Yes.”

“Ahaha. Rather than talking about my magic essence, let’s talk about Rodania’s hero instead. And about the letter to deliver to your home, Professor.” Rio smiled wryly and redirected the wandering conversation back on track.

“...Right,” Celia agreed tiredly. “I have an idea with regards to the letter. There’s a hidden passageway from the back of the estate to the main house... If we use that, we should be able to place the letter and return without a problem.”

“I see. Then it seems like it’d be better to have you guide us into your home, Professor.” Rio looked at Celia dependently.

“Yup, leave it to me,” Celia agreed proudly.

“Which only leaves the problem of sneaking into Rodania... Could you wait somewhere safe during that time, Professor?” Rio asked.

“Yeah. If something bad happens, I’d only get in the way anyway. If only I’d mastered the art of self defense...”

No matter how much magic she could use, Celia hadn’t trained for combat as a soldier. There was no guarantee she could launch offensive magic without hesitation against someone during a battle, and she was powerless in close-range combat. If someone closed in on her, she’d be no different than any other defenseless civilian.

Rio thought for a moment. “Would you like me to teach you some simple self defense? Of course, Aishia and I will be the ones protecting you normally, but there might be a use for it if we’re walking outside,” he suggested.

“...You’re right. It wouldn’t be good for me to stay shut inside, either. Would you, please?” Celia was more of the indoor type, but she agreed with his assessment.

“Then once we get back from Count Claire’s, we can start the lessons along with the ones on sorcery and spirit arts.”

Celia nodded. “Okay. You’ve also promised to teach me cooking. It’s like our roles have completely reversed... I was the teacher in the past, fufu,” she said, smiling in amusement.

“You’re still my Professor to me, even now.” Rio said, beaming cheerily.

◇　◇　◇

Two days later, after lunch...

Rio carried Celia as he and Aishia flew through the air to visit the capital of Count Claire’s territory, Cleia.

Cleia was located towards the east of the Beltrum Kingdom, a regional city that the main road towards Galarc Kingdom passed through. It was Rio’s first time visiting.

With roughly 30,000 people, the regional city boasted a medium-sized population and functioned as an important trading point between the east and west sides of Beltrum.

Rio entered the city from the eastern side, holding hands with the two girls as they walked down the main road. “Since we’ll be sneaking into the estate at nighttime, how about we go somewhere before then?” Rio asked Celia, who was walking on his right side.

Cleia was Celia’s hometown; it was possible that she had memories that she wanted to revisit, Rio thought, but Celia shook her head.

“No, it’s okay. There may be people who know me, so I’m fine with just looking at the town like this,” she said. Her cloak hood covered her face and made it hard to see her expression, but she looked somewhat downcast to Rio.

“Let’s walk, then. I’m hungry. We should go eat something yummy.” From Rio’s left, Aishia looked at the two of them and pulled at Rio’s arm. She may have been trying to cheer Celia up in her own way.

“...Good idea. How about that, Professor? If there are any local specialties, we can go eat that.” Rio smiled faintly and tugged Celia along by the hand.

“Ah, wait! Hold on, you two.” Despite giving a verbal objection, Celia was smiling happily as she allowed the two to lead her forward.

Thus, time passed in the blink of an eye. As they walked around and tried different foods, twilight eventually settled upon the city.

At the moment, the three of them were drinking tea in a rather trendy cafe while taking a break. Sitting on the second floor terrace, they watched the people walking through the city with the sun setting behind them, eating their extra orders of dessert.

“I may have eaten a little too much after all,” Rio said with a strained smile, holding a hand against his stomach.

“Y-Yeah. It was delicious, but maybe this scone was a bit too much. There’s no way I’m eating dinner now. Ugh, I’ll have to go on a diet...” Celia agreed, hanging her head with guilt.

“It was good,” Aishia said. As a spirit, she could change her food intake into magic essence, so she could easily eat as much as she wanted without ever gaining weight.

“Just what kind of body does a spirit have? I’m so jealous...” Celia pouted, looking at Aishia.

“The materialization of a physical body from a spiritual existence is a spirit art unique to spirits alone. I don’t know if I have the organs necessary for human life to function, but my general structure and physical abilities shouldn’t vary too much from a normal human,” Aishia said, giving a rather serious answer unexpectedly. Celia was left taken aback in surprise.

“H-Huh... Really...”

“The more a spirit art causes a phenomena that goes against the laws of nature, the greater the essence consumed. Taking on the physical nature of a form may be the most natural way of materialization, I believe,” Rio explained, adding on his own assumption.

“That makes sense. Even in sorcery, phenomena that contradict nature’s laws will affect the essence consumption...” Celia murmured as she started to lose herself in her own thoughts. Figuring she wouldn’t be paying attention for a while, Rio smiled wryly.

“It’s almost getting dark,” Aishia said.

Rio thought for a moment. “...Let’s wait a little longer. There’re still lots of people on the streets, so at least wait until my stomach settles,” he laughed, deciding to extend their break time.

◇　◇　◇

Nearly an hour passed after their visit to the cafe. With the exception of the main road, the streets were completely empty of people as Rio and the girls made their way to the Claire estate.

The estate sat at the top of a small hill, its interior lit by torches as soldiers patrolled the area. Any amateur would easily be discovered by the security measures; however, Rio and Aishia blended into the darkness as they flew with their spirit arts, landing in a corner of the estate without being spotted by anyone.

“Do you think we can make it to the hidden passageway without being seen? If not, we can always try sneaking in from the rooftop instead...” Rio whispered, letting Celia down as he observed the state of the estate grounds from between the bushes.

“It’ll be fine — the entrance is located in an area hard to spot.”

“All right. Then please lead the way.”

“Okay. Follow me,” Celia nodded, bending down low as she began to move. Rio and Aishia brought up the rear while staying alert of the presence of any patrolling soldiers.

Roughly one minute later, they stopped moving. “It’s the fountain over there. The ground behind the estate is the entrance of the hidden passageway,” Celia said, pointing to a fountain on the outskirts of the garden.

“I see. It doesn’t seem like there are any patrols around, but just in case... May I hold you for a little while?” Rio asked, peering at the garden from the shadows.

“Huh...?” Celia stiffened out of bewilderment.

“There’s a chance we may be spotted while moving from here to that fountain, so I’d like to hide us with spirit arts just in case,” Rio explained.

“O-Ohh, that’s what you meant. Just like the spirit arts Aishia used when we were getting away from the capital, right? Sure, go ahead,” Celia said in understanding, having an idea of the spirit art that would be used. It seemed like Aishia had already used it on her once before, when Rio was acting as a diversion in the capital.

“If you don’t mind, then,” Rio said, picking Celia up in his arms. Then he turned to Aishia. “Let’s go, Aishia.”

“Okay. I’ll use the spirit arts, then.”

“Please do. Thank you, Aishia.”

“No worries,” Aishia said, activating her spirit arts. Immediately afterwards, a gentle breeze blew around them, completely enveloping Rio.

“Let’s go,” he said, walking forward. Aishia followed behind him.

“...Hey, Rio. You can see your surroundings, right?” Celia asked quietly, still being carried. She couldn’t see their surroundings at all — it was as though there was a thick fog in the air, distorting the space.

“Yes. If you train yourself to visualize magic essence, you’d be able to see, too, Professor,” Rio explained.

The spirit art Aishia was currently using was a wind-based invisibility illusion that weaved her magic essence into the surrounding air. It created a unique space that caused those within the space to appear transparent to the outside. Unlike with turning into spirit form, their physical bodies were still present, so it wasn’t possible to shut sounds and presences out, too. Furthermore, exterior interference and contact could easily shake the space, so they weren’t able to make any sudden or vigorous movements, like running and jumping.

Other than that, people who could visualize essence could see through the spirit art’s activation and view the interior of the space, while people with high sensitivity for detecting magic essence could also feel the displacement, so there was a limit to its use.

That being said, barely any humans in the Strahl region could visually detect magic essence, so it was a worthwhile ability to use.

Thus, they blended in with the surroundings and moved towards the fountain.

“Aishia, the splashing water will make the space shake. You can undo it now,” Rio said.

“Okay.” After Aishia undid the spirit art, Celia’s vision returned to normal.

“Just in case a guard comes, I’ll leave you to unlock the entrance, Professor.”

Prompted by Rio, Celia immediately began searching around the floor. “Leave it to me. It should be around here...”

Then, after a moment, Celia discovered the entrance to the hidden passageway. “Here it is!”

She moved her hands and pressed against the stone tiles on the ground, moving it towards the side like a sliding door. However, Celia lacked the strength to move the stone tile easily.

“Let me help. I just have to pull it this way, right?” Rio asked, promptly offering to assist her.

“Yeah, thank you...” No sooner than Celia had nodded, Rio was lightly moving the stone tile to the side, revealing the hidden stairway down to the house.

“I’m going to close it,” Rio said as they headed down.

“Yes, please. I’ll just light the place...” As Rio closed the entrance back up, Celia fiddled with the magic artifacts in the underground corridor to give the passageway light.

“Let’s go.”

“Okay.”

They headed down the passageway; at the end of the long and narrow corridor was a wide, open space. It was probably directly below or very close to the house.

“I’m lighting the lanterns,” Celia said, activating the artifacts in the room. The lights on the ceiling immediately lit up, illuminating the space. Directly opposite the corridor from the fountain was a set of stairs leading up to the upper floors; it was lined with several doors on either side.

“It’s very spacious,” Rio noted, looking around the room curiously.

“No one other than my family comes here, so don’t worry. The doors on the left and right lead to the kitchen, bedrooms, and emergency living spaces. The stairs directly before us lead to the house, exiting at father and mother’s bedroom,” Celia said, explaining the structure of the underground room to Rio.

“I see. Then shall I leave your letter in your parents’ room? If they’re present, then we can also possibly arrange for you to meet them...” Rio asked, observing Celia’s expression.

“...No, don’t. The two of them should be in the capital right now. Mother regularly cleans this place out, so you can leave it here instead. The servants sometimes go into the bedroom, too.” Celia shook her head and took the letter out of the pocket of her cloak.

“...I understand.” Rio was about to suggest they wait around until her parents returned, but he swallowed his words and agreed instead. It was possible that Celia hadn’t completely organized her feelings yet, after all.

“Thank you, Rio.” Celia smiled softly.

“No problem. Let’s come see them some other time.”

We definitely will, Rio vowed to himself and returned Celia’s smile.

Chapter 5: Infiltrating Rodania

Several hours after Liselotte’s airship left Beltrant harbor...

Rio, Celia, and Aishia had departed from Cleia, the capital of Count Claire’s territory, and made their way to Rodania, Marquess Rodan’s territory located to the northeast of the Kingdom of Beltrum. They flew through the air with spirit arts and looked down on the town from a distance.

“It’s smaller than Cleia in size, but it’s been built rather sturdily,” Rio said, voicing his first impression.

“Marquess Rodan’s territory borders both the Proxia Empire to the north and the Galarc Kingdom to the east, after all. It’s a vital location in terms of the military... That’s why the city has also been fortified as a citadel. Perhaps it was the perfect place for Duke Huguenot’s faction to establish themselves?” Celia explained. Though she may have been a shut-in researcher of sorcery, she wasn’t a noble for nothing. She was fairly knowledgeable about the geography of every region.

“I expected as much, but I guess I’ll need to prepare myself for this. Let’s land somewhere outside the city first. I’ll take out the stone house so you two can wait inside, and I’ll come back once before it gets dark.”

“Okay.”

“Got it.”

At Rio’s suggestion, Aishia and Celia both nodded in unison.

◇　◇　◇

After landing outside the city and setting up the stone house, Rio snuck into Rodania alone in broad daylight. He jumped over a section of outer wall that was relatively unguarded and blended in with the crowds of people inside the city.

Rodania was currently estranged from the Beltrum government, but the city was still bustling with life. It was possible that the possession of Princess Flora and appearance of the hero had an influence on the people, but if those governing the place were truly vicious, then the city certainly wouldn’t be this lively.

Is this the work of Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan? I didn’t have a very good impression of them, but...

From his past experience of being falsely accused during his time in the Beltrum Royal Academy, Rio’s impression of the two noble families governing this land had been one of brutality and cunningness. However, their reign seemed rather peaceful on the outside.

That being said, cruel and cunning members of nobility were better at hiding their visible flaws.

After Rio had observed a reasonable amount of the city’s state, he began to gather information. First, he needed to know if the hero was really summoned in this land — and whether or not that fact was announced officially or not. For that, he decided to start with his usual chatting up of stall owners through purchasing their products. First, he went to make an order at a skewer stand.

“I heard through the grapevine that a hero appeared in this land, is that true?” Rio said to the stall owner as though he was casually gossiping.

“Yeah, it’s true. There was a hero summoned here in Rodania,” the stall owner said with a friendly smile.

“...So it’s true, huh. Is that a well-known fact?”

“Of course — it’s a well-known story around here. A huge pillar of light shot up from the depths of the district where the nobles live. That was when the hero was spotted, apparently.”

“What kind of person is the hero? Like their name, or...” Rio asked boldly.

“Ah, sorry. I don’t know that much.” The skewer stall owner shook his head apologetically.

“No no, I was just asking out of curiosity.”

“Hahaha, the heroes are the disciples of the Six Wise Gods, after all... Makes sense that you’d be curious. You seem to have a pretty devout sense of faith there, kid. You’re young, yet you mind your manners.”

“Ah, thank you...” Rio smiled faintly and tried to avoid elaborating. The stall owner must have mistaken him for a devoted believer of the Six Wise Gods, but he decided to go along with the misunderstanding, as it was convenient.

After Rio finished eating the grilled skewer, he continued his search for information. However, he was unable to figure out the name of the hero, and had to place his hopes on the night infiltration instead.

◇　◇　◇

That night, Rio returned to the stone house and brought Aishia back to Rodania with him. Celia watched the house alone.

The city of Rodania had completely fallen dim, flickering under the light of torchfire. Rio looked down at the city from the skies above.

“First, let’s approach the estate. We’ll communicate in telepathy from here onwards.”

They began their infiltration immediately, slowly lowering their altitude. Their destination was the estate on the cliff at the very furthest end of the noble district; its appearance was like that of a stronghold, built like a sturdy fortress. Behind the cliff was a large lake that sustained Rodania with water.

Rio confirmed the strict state of the security and gave Aishia instructions to close in on the rooftop. ...Let’s go down to the roof of the estate first.

Okay.

Covered in their black cloaks, the two of them blended with the darkness and landed on the roof. Then, I’ll be off now.

Aishia would first sneak into the consulate and sound out the hero’s location and surrounding security. She turned into her spirit form.

Make sure you take extra care against sensory type artifacts and barriers, Rio said with worry in his voice. No matter how much she could change into her spirit form, there were areas where even Aishia would have difficulty getting into. When it came to places with strict precautions for detecting sorcery set up, spirit forms made of ode were in danger of being detected.

Aishia nodded. Got it. Faint particles of light scattered as she turned into her spirit form. Only the black cloak she had been wearing remained, fluttering gently to the rooftop.

Contact me immediately if anything happens, Rio said, retrieving Aishia’s cloak.

Aishia nodded again.Yup.

A long time passed. Rio hid any and all inklings of his presence and waited silently on the rooftop.

Haruto, I can’t find the hero’s location, Aishia’s said telepathically.

...You can’t find it? You mean there’s no one around that seems like a hero? Rio asked, finding that strange.

Yeah. Not within the range I can move, anyway, Aishia confirmed.

You mean there were rooms or areas you couldn’t enter because of detection artifacts or barriers?

Yup.

Then it’ll be impossible to get in without being noticed, I guess. No, it’s possible the hero has moved away from Rodania too... Rio thought, processing the situation. All right. Can you come back here first? I’ll come along this time, do you think you can show me the way? I want to at least confirm the hero’s name before we go back today.

Within a minute, Aishia had returned to Rio and the two of them snuck inside together. All right, let’s go.

This way — it’s easiest to get inside from the rooftop via the watchtower.

The two of them began to move, Aishia leading the way in her material form by pulling Rio’s hand. They cast wind spirit arts along the way to make themselves invisible and approached the watchtower.

We have to enter carefully so the guards inside don’t notice us, Rio said through their telepathic connection, listening carefully to the watchtower. Guards were chatting idly amongst themselves.

“Man, I’m so bored. Nothing ever happens.”

“I know, right?”

“Tell me a funny story.”

“I don’t know any. Shouldn’t you know some?”

“If I did, I would have told them to you ages ago.”

There seemed to be two guards in total.

They’ve got their guards completely lowered. We should be fine to go, Rio thought, about to give Aishia the direction to go, when one of the guards suddenly spoke up.

“The hero sure has it nice, always bringing beautiful women with him everywhere.”

Rio froze on the spot, trying to listen to more of their conversation.

“Beautiful women? You dumbass. Watch your mouth. That’s the Second Princess and a duke’s daughter you’re talking about, you realize? If anyone heard you say that...”

“Nobody’s listening. Anyway, that hero took those two girls and went somewhere, didn’t he? Sure must be nice. He looks like he’s even younger than me, too...” One of the guards started complaining, and the other guard sighed and agreed sympathetically.

“...Well, I can understand why you feel that way... But compared to them, we live in a completely different world.”

So the hero’s left Rodania now, huh? Then there’s no need to force our way inside the estate. If I could at least find out his name...

Rio decided to hang around in the hope that one of the guards would say the hero’s name out loud.

“I wish I could meet someone too...”

“How about one of the maids?” But the conversation didn’t go in the direction that he hoped. Rio finally ran out of patience.

Aishia. It’s a little risky, but I’m going to cast an illusion on the two guards in the tower. I’ll use a wind spirit art to hypnotize them.

All right. Will I need to do so, too? Rio shook his head with a smile. It’s okay. You can just watch.

With a deep breath, he focused on gathering essence in his hands and sent a faint breeze towards the watchtower. Roughly one minute later, the panicked voice of a guard in the tower could be heard.

“...Hey, I suddenly really need to take a piss.”

“Ah, you too? I need to go, too, actually...” The other guard also announced in a restless voice.

Seems like it worked. Rio chuckled when the effect of the hypnosis became obvious. Since he wasn’t in direct contact with his target, he couldn’t cast a very strong hypnotic spell and it took some time for the effect to take place, but everything went as expected.

“Could I step away for a sec?”

“No fair! I want to go too!”

“I-I was the one who asked first, right? I’ll be back as soon as I can, so... Please?!”

“Guh... F-Fine, but make it quick!”

“Thanks!”

With that exchange, one of the guards dashed off with haste.

Let’s go. This time, I’ll place the remaining guard in a waking dream and have him tell me the hero’s name.

Leave that to me. Aishia took the lead and moved first.

The events that happened after that were a splendid display of skill. Aishia snuck into the watchtower easily, holding the guard’s head from behind him as she activated her illusion. After spending a few seconds confirming the guard’s mind was controlled, Rio snuck into the watchtower next.

The guard gazed at Rio blankly, caught in the illusion. “O-Oh, you’re back! That was rather... fast?” he said, face brightening happily. He seemed to have mistaken Rio for his coworker that had gone to the toilet first.

“No, I actually haven’t gone yet. I wanted to ask you for the hero’s name first.”

The guard looked at Rio impatiently. “H-Huh?! What the hell, man. Now’s not the time for that...!”

“I know, but it’s important. I’ll go as soon as you tell me.”

“I-Isn’t it Hiroaki Sakata?”

“Hiroaki Sakata... Have you heard of the names Satsuki Sumeragi or Takahisa Sendo at all?” Rio asked with a serious look.

“No!” The guard yelled angrily.

“...I see. Don’t worry then. I’ll be back soon.” With those words, Rio had what he came for and turned away.

Let’s go, Aishia, he said through telepathy.

Okay. Aishia promptly let go of the man’s head, and Rio swiftly jumped out of the watchtower. Aishia followed close behind.

The guard’s unfocused gaze vacantly stared at nothing for a while, but he eventually snapped back to his senses.

“...Eh? What?”

Meanwhile, Rio and Aishia had already flown away from the roof and were soaring through the skies, and the other guard returned to the watchtower, done with his business.

“Phew... Hey, I’m back.”

The guard that had been placed under a waking dream tilted his head curiously. “...Didn’t you come back once before?”

“Huh? What are you on about? Anyways, didn’t you need to go too?”

“...O-Oh, right! I’ll be right back!“ The guard who had been placed under the illusion dashed off towards the toilet.

◇　◇　◇

While Liselotte and the others were steadily proceeding down the road...

Far in the skies above, the Proxia Empire ambassador, Reiss, was flying along clad in his black cloak. The security’s turned out heavier than I expected. Duke Huguenot’s faction’s accompaniment was completely unplanned for. It was all well and good sending the Evil Black Wyvern ahead to interrupt their business, but now what...

Reiss observed Liselotte’s party with sharp eyes; below him, Liselotte and the others showed no sign of awareness about Reiss’ presence above their heads as they traveled to Amande.

The original goal was to only capture Liselotte Cretia, but this makes the attack much more difficult to set up. However, Princess Flora’s presence is a welcome surprise. If handled carefully, this situation could allow for us to control the relationship between the Huguenot faction and the Galarc Kingdom, Reiss thought to himself with a cold smirk to his mouth. There was no way he was passing up this opportunity.

Which means I’ll have to splurge a little. I wanted to save this for the attack on Amande, but it’ll be good to test how far the current heroes have grown, too.

Not much time had passed since their departed from Nor, so Reiss leisurely pondered when he should launch his plan with a pleasant look in his eyes. He decided to observe them for a little longer.

A large magic circle spanning several meters immediately appeared before Aria. Light from the magic circle gathered in Aria’s hand and, after a beat, a thick beam of essence shot forward. The monsters that were closing in from the front were instantly blown away.

“Wha...” Seeing that spectacle left some of the knights gaping in surprise — Aria had just used a higher middle-grade offensive magic.

It consumed much more essence compared to what it took to learn, but it had a weakness in how it was difficult to cast, and took time to activate depending on the user’s ability. However, its power was guaranteed. The knights had been surprised at how an attendant had been able to acquire such a powerful magic, and that Aria’s activation time was fairly short. But they only had a brief moment to be surprised, as in the very next moment, Aria suddenly disappeared.

Without the use of Augendae Corporis, Aria closed in on the monsters at an inhuman speed. The secret to her speed lay in the enchanted sword she wielded — an ancient artifact class of enchanted sword, to be precise. The enchanted blade Aria held glowed faintly along the blade where a formula had been carved in, granting the wielder the effects of a physical enhancement sorcery.

“Gwah?” The head of one of the monsters closing in on the front of their formation went flying. Two, three, four, and five heads went flying one after another in rapid succession.

The monsters didn’t seem to realize their heads were being cut off, each severed head wearing a curious expression. However, once that head fell to the floor and gazed upon the sight of their detached body standing before them, they realized the truth. One beat later, the body of the monsters that had been beheaded would snap and collapse. In the blink of an eye, they turned to dust, leaving nothing but an enchanted gem behind.

Meanwhile, Cosette watched Aria’s battle from beside the carriage.

“That’s the Reaper Princess for you. So reliable,” she said with a smile on her face, voicing Aria’s other nickname.

Natalie looked at Cosette in exasperation. “...Damned fool. It’d be your head flying if she heard you.”

“Ahaha. It’s fine, it’s fine. At this distance, she can’t...” Cosette laughed lightly. However, from where she was fighting several meters away, Aria met her eyes for an instant, making her freeze.

“S-She didn’t hear me, right?” Cosette said with a twitch.

Natalie shook her head bluntly. “Dunno. More importantly, we should follow our orders and start fighting, too,” she said, looking between the forest on the left and the right. The monsters to the sides had also been distracted by Aria’s fighting prowess, but they were slowly returning to the task at hand, raising their voices as they glared at the knights.

“...Right. Grace!” Cosette nodded with a sigh, calling the name of another attendant nearby.

“What?!” Grace replied with a grim look.

“Natalie, Chloe, and I will handle the monsters on the right. The four of you take care of the monsters on the left. You’ll be in charge of that side.”

“Understood. Here we go! Augendae Corporis!” Cosette said. Grace immediately followed suit, chanting the magic spell to enhance her physical abilities. The other attendants successively chanted the spell, too; once they did, magic circles appeared around their bodies, revolving in circles as they enveloped their bodies and activated magic to enhance the caster’s physical abilities. Grace and the other attendants ran off — Once Cosette confirmed that, she turned to issue orders to the trainee attendant.

“Chloe, you stay alert of the front while using Photon Projectilis to take out the small fry from behind the knights on the right side. If you see any monsters throwing stones, prioritize aiming for them first. Start from the enemies at the edge, so you don’t accidentally hit any allies, okay?”

“Okay!“ Chloe responded with a stiff voice.

“Now, shall we get going, Natalie?” Cosette readied her halberd and smiled devilishly. Natalie held her two daggers and nodded,

“Yes, I’m ready to go whenever.”

“Augendae Corporis—” Cosette and Natalie chanted in unison.

After the magic circle rose and enhanced their abilities, the two of them immediately ran towards the forest.

◇　◇　◇

As the hectic battle unfolded below, Reiss was overlooking the state of the fight from where he floated high above.

There’s one... rather incredible woman present. Liselotte Cretia’s confidant, I assume. Goodness, if this isn’t one tough guard. If I don’t approach this carefully, she might just defeat me... What a bad matchup.

Reiss looked down at Aria with his sharp eyes; she was overwhelming the monsters. At this rate, she would exterminate all the monsters coming from the front all by herself.

The guard on the left and right is also tough. While they’re not as notable as the woman in front, Liselotte Cretia’s subordinates are all talented. Thanks to their work, the flustered knights to the sides have also calmed down and started reacting properly. It seems like they’ve completely regained any advantage we had of our surprise attack.

Most of the knights were lined up along the side with their shields up, creating a barricade as though they were on high alert for a surprise attack from the side. On top of that, Liselotte’s proud attendants were massacring monsters quite far forward, so taking down that barricade would be no easy feat.

But there are still weak points. Where to aim... Reiss thought, looking at the rear of the formation.

There, the commanding officer, Raymond, was leading several other knights to stop the progression of the monsters. They were using Photon Projectilis to take out the numerous small-sized goblins and only making contact with the larger-sized orcs to repel them. Compared to the front of the formation, it would be easier to take down this side.

The girl at the front is eliminating the monsters at a much faster rate than expected. It seems the goblins and the orcs don’t stand a chance. Although, that depends on how they’re used... Reiss groaned quietly, looking at Aria once more.

Princess Flora and Liselotte Cretia are inside a carriage, though I don’t know which of the two, and it should be safe to assume the hero is riding alongside them, too. Although, there are no signs of him stepping forward for now... He thought deeply, looking down at the two carriages lined below his eyes.

For now, I’ll have the projectile squad focus their aim on the second carriage and send reinforcements to the sides. If he really refuses to show up, then I’ll simply pierce through the carriage from here. Reiss chuckled pleasantly to himself.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, inside the carriage where Liselotte and the others were hiding, Hiroaki was sitting on the floor of the carriage with his knees to his chest, tapping a leg restlessly.

“Oi, what’s going on outside? Is everything all right?” It was the umpteenth time he was asking the three girls that question.

“It’s fine. My attendants outside are the elite of the elite, especially Aria. And all of the knights of Duke Huguenot’s faction are there, too.” Liselotte nodded firmly in a calm tone, easing Hiroaki’s excitement at what was his first real combat experience.

“...Ah, but... like... Are the roads of this world really so dangerous? It’s been a while since the attack started and there are so many people out there, so how come the battle hasn’t ended yet?” Hiroaki objected gruffly, looking around the carriage somewhat nervously.

His fears stemmed from the fact that even now, at this moment, loud orders and angry yelling were still being exchanged outside. The fact that the number of stones hitting the carriage had increased wasn’t reassuring, either.

“Hero, let us believe in those outside,” Flora said.

“Unfortunately, the situation is like this right now. Those outside still haven’t explained what’s going on to us, and I’m not about to believe some people I don’t even know. Anyone who does is an idiot. Who would take responsibility for this?” Hiroaki had completely lost his cool, raising his voice in irritation. The girls around him were worried, too, but he seemed to be the only one who considered himself a victim, demanding someone take blame for their current state.

“...Okay,” Flora hung her head dejectedly.

The ones attacking us are monsters... I’d much prefer if he went outside and yelled his abuse at them instead. He’s just saying what he wants right now. After all that talk about protecting us, when it comes to the real thing he turns like this? What happened to your pride, the Yamata no Orochi? Geez! Liselotte wanted to rant at Hiroaki, but instead let out a small exasperated sigh. She then reached out and squeezed Flora’s hand.

“Huh?” Flora looked up in surprise at Liselotte’s face.

“Forgive me. Embarrassing as it is to admit, I’m a little afraid. Could I please hold your hand for a little while, Princess Flora?” Liselotte said, smiling gently at Flora.

“...Yes!” Flora nodded in relief. Seeing the two girls’ frail exchange finally made Hiroaki realize something.

“Ah, you must be scared, too, Roanna. Don’t worry... If it comes down to it, I’ll release my Yamata no Orochi and protect you.” Hiroaki held Roanna’s hand rather guiltily.

“I knew I could count on you,” Roanna said, leaning on Hiroaki.

After that, a silence fell over the carriage for a while. However, unable to endure the silence, Hiroaki opened his mouth.

“...But with the outside situation as chaotic as it is, having no idea of what’s going on isn’t very good. What is the commanding officer thinking?”

“I completely agree. Once the battle has ended, I shall make a report to the commanding officer,” Roanna said without missing a beat.

“Good, that — Whoa! That was a big one just now.” Hiroaki nodded, when a stone hit the carriage with a clang. That seemed to reignite Hiroaki’s concerns. “...Oi oi, this carriage might be covered in a layer of steel, but isn’t the higher elevation making it easier to aim for?” he muttered in frustration.

“It’ll be okay. Mere stones wouldn’t be able to pierce the walls of this carriage,” Flora said encouragingly, but —

“But doesn’t that mean if something more than a stone comes flying, we’ll be in trouble? Do you have proof that won’t happen? We should act in preparation for the worst. I think it’s too risky remaining in one place when we our communications with the outside have been cut off.” Hiroaki’s thoughts had completely taken a negative turn. On top of that, he was no longer calm.

Good grief, what a bothersome personality he has. Liselotte furrowed her brow in vexation. Preparing for the worst case in an emergency wasn’t a bad thing in itself, but becoming aggressive and forcing your emotions on your surroundings was horrible.

No matter how many opposite opinions were offered, a hot tempered person like him would not be likely to lend an ear to any of it. If anything, he’d just get more stubborn and heated about it.

Just then — Ba-doom! A particularly loud impact struck the roof of the carriage, shaking it greatly. “Whoa!”

“Kyah!” Hiroaki and Flora couldn’t hold back their screams. Liselotte hurriedly held Flora close to her to protect her, when she suddenly looked up.

W-What?!

The steel plated ceiling had a huge dent in the middle.

“Wha... What fell on us just now?! There better not be a monster above us!” Hiroaki’s eyes widened in shock as he wailed.

“I don’t know!” Liselotte finally cried out, at a loss.

There’s no helping it... I’ll go outside and find out what happened. It would normally be unthinkable for the subject of an escort to voluntarily step out into the battlefield, but this emergency surpassed that custom.

However, just as Liselotte resolved herself, Hiroaki’s patience reached its limit. “Kuh! E-Enough already! I can’t stay in here any longer without knowing what’s going on outside! We’re going outside, you guys!”

He materialized the Divine Arms, Yamata no Orochi, inside the cramped carriage. Hiroaki gripped it tightly as he took Roanna by the hand and flung open the door.

“S-Sir Hiroaki?! Please hold on!” Roanna admonished him, but he didn’t listen. He jumped out of the carriage, leaving Liselotte and Flora behind.

“Hero?! Argh, how troublesome! Geez!” Liselotte frowned in annoyance as she stood up. Flora had lost her composure in her confusion.

“U-Umm, what should we do?! We have to follow the hero!”

“...We’re going to check on what’s happening outside. Make sure you do not leave my side.” Liselotte hesitated for a second before taking Flora’s hand and helping her up. She had considered leaving her inside the carriage, but it could create more of an issue if they were split up.

“O-Okay!”